A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 6, Accession 2017:070 FA1523
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1982-2013; 1
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - Bayou Bend Collection of American Art Catalog, 1984-1998 (Box 70, Folder 456)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - "Duncan Phyfe: Master Cabinetmaker in New York" Exhibition, 2010-2013 (Box 43, Folder 253-254)
  - Museum of Modern Art - American Drawings Catalog, 1983-1996 (Box 71, Folder 457)
  - Museum of Modern Art - "De Kooning: A Retrospective" Exhibition and Catalog, 2009-2013 (Box 43, Folder 255-256)
  - Museum Loan Network, Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Energizing the Study of Early American Art, 2004-2007 (Box 43, Folder 257-258)
  - Mystic Seaport Museum - "America and the Sea: Treasures from the Collections of the Mystic Seaport Museum" Publication, 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 259)
  - National Academy of Design - "Surrealism U.S.A" Exhibition, 2004-2007 (Box 44, Folder 260)
  - National Academy Museum - "Luminist Horizons: The Art and Collection of James A. Suydam" Exhibition and Catalog, 2005-2007 (Box 44, Folder 261)
  - The National Bureau of Asian Research - Policy Research Fellowship on Asia, 2005-2013 (Box 44, Folder 262-263)
  - The National Bureau of Asian Research - Policy Research Fellowship on Asia (Renewal), 2008-2012 (Box 44, Folder 264-265)
  - National Committee on American Foreign Policy - United States-China-Taiwan Roundtable on United States-China Policy, 2004-2007 (Box 44, Folder 266)
  - National Gallery of Art - "American Paintings of the Nineteenth Century" Volume II, 1995-2000 (Box 71, Folder 458)
  - National Gallery of Art - "Hudson River School Visions: The Landscapes of Sanford R. Gifford" Exhibition, 2002-2005 (Box 45, Folder 267-268)
  - National Museum of American Art - Survey of Outdoor Sculptures, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 459)
  - New Britain Museum of Art - Reinterpretation and Reinstallation of Permanent Collection, 2003-2006 (Box 45, Folder 269)
  - New Museum of Contemporary Art - Marcia Tucker Collection, 2004-2005 (Box 45, Folder 270)
  - New Orleans Museum of Art - "Passionate Visions of the American South: Self-Taught Artists from 1940 to the Present", 1995-1997 (Box 71, Folder 460)
  - New-York Historical Society - "John Rogers: American Stories" Exhibition and Catalog, 2008-2013 (Box 45, Folder 271)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - New York City Youth Funders Network, 2004-2006 (Box 45, Folder 272)
  - New York University, Center for Religion and Media - "Digital Religion: Transforming Knowledge and Practice" Project, 2009-2013 (Box 45, Folder 273)
  - New York University, Center on Law and Security - "The Constitution and National Security: The First Amendment Under Attack?" Conference, 2010-2013 (Box 46, Folder 274)
  - New York University - Initiative on Religion and Politics in the Americas, 2009-2013 (Box 46, Folder 275-276)
  - New York State Historical Association - "Artist and Visionary: William Matthew Prior Revealed" Exhibition and Catalog, 2011-2013 (Box 46, Folder 277)
  - New York Women's Foundation - Annual Grants Breakfast Publications, 1987-2002 (Box 71, Folder 461-462, Box 72, Folder 463)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art - Reinterpret and Reinstall American Art Collection, 2007-2013 (Box 46, Folder 278)
  - Oberlin College - Workshop on the History of the Book in East Asia, 2011-2013 (Box 46, Folder 279)
  - Olana Partnership - "Treasures from Olana: Landscapes by Frederic Edwin Church" Exhibition and Catalog, 2004-2007 (Box 47, Folder 280-281)
  - Orange County Museum of Art - "Richard Diebenkorn: The Ocean Park Series, 1967-1988" Exhibition and Catalog, 2009-2013 (Box 47, Folder 282)
  - Peabody Essex Museum - Asian Photography Collection, 1999-2006 (Box 47, Folder 283)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - Narrative and Portrait Paintings Catalogs, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 464)
  - Pewabic Pottery - Archives, 2012-2013 (Box 47, Folder 284)
  - Philadelphia Futures - College Preparatory Program, 1999-2003 (Box 72, Folder 466)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - "Guide to the Thomas Eakins Research Collection with a Lifetime Exhibition Record and Bibliography", 1982-1997 (Box 72, Folder 467-468)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Offset Endowment Loses for Key American Art Curators, Supplement Collection Research, and Bolster the American Art Fellowship Program (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2013 (Box 47, Folder 285)
  - Phillips Collection - "The Eye of Duncan Phillips: A Collection of Making", 1999 (Box 72, Folder 465)
  - Pomona College - Pacific Basin Institute, 1997-2006 (Box 47, Folder 286)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - "Henry Ossawa Tanner: Modern Spirit" Exhibition and Catalog, 2009-2013 (Box 48, Folder 287)
  - Portland Museum of Art - Reinterpret and Reinstall American Art Collection, 2002-2008 (Box 48, Folder 288)
  - Portland Museum of Art - "Rockwell Kent: The Mythic and the Modern" Exhibition and Catalog, 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 289)
  - Portland Museum of Art - "Weatherbeaten: Winslow Homer and Maine" Exhibition and Catalog, 2010-2013 (Box 48, Folder 290)
  - Posse Foundation - Urban Minority Students, 2000-2003 (Box 72, Folder 469)
  - Presbyterian College and Theological Seminary - Center for International Cooperation, 1997-2002 (Box 48, Folder 291-292, Box 49, Folder 293)
  - Presbyteries of Boise, Eastern Oregon and Kendall - Pastor-at-Large Program, 2001-2003 (Box 49, Folder 294)
  - Princeton in Asia - 100th Anniversary, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 295)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Bryant M. Kirkland Minister of the Chapel, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 296)
  - Princeton University - Chinese Rare Books Project, 1998-2005 (Box 49, Folder 297)
  - Princeton University, Art Musem - John B. Elliot Collection of Chinese Calligraphy, 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 298)
  - Public Interest Law Institute - Southeast Asians in the International Public Interest Law Fellows Program, 2011-2013 (Box 49, Folder 299)
  - Queens Library Foundation - "Visible Traces: Rare Books and Special Collections from the National Library of China", 1999-2000 (Box 49, Folder 300)
  - Religion in American Life - Office Relocation, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 301)
  - Research Libraries Group - Worldwide Access to Chinese and Asian Language Databases, 1998-2001 (Box 49, Folder 302)
  - Reynolda House Museum of American Art - Art Exchange Program (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1997-2003 (Box 49, Folder 303)
  - Reynolda House Museum of American Art - Collections Related Positions, 2011-2013 (Box 50, Folder 304-305)
  - Rockefeller University - David Rockefeller Professorship, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 306)
  - Lauren Rogers Museum of Art - Native American Basket Collection (American Collections Enhancements (ACE) Initiative), 1999-2006 (Box 50, Folder 307-308)
  - Milton Rosenbluth Fund - Physician's Travel Grants, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 309)
  - Royal Oak Foundation - Luce Garden Lecture Series, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 310)
  - Rural Development Institute - China's Agrarian Reforms, 2001-2004 (Box 50, Folder 311-312)
  - St. Andrew's-Sewanee School - Theodore Roosevelt High School Summer Program, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 313-314)
  - St. George's Society of New York - "The British in New York since 1770" Exhibition, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 315)
  - St. Joseph's Seminary - Pre-College Language Program, 1997-2001 (Box 51, Folder 316)
  - St. Mary's Seminary and University - Raymond Brown Professorship in Biblical Studies and International Conference, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 317-318)
  - St. Paul College, Quezon City - Construction of Father Louis Chauvet Chapel and the Father James Reuter, S.J. Theater, 2000-2002 (Box 52, Folder 319)
  - St. Vladimir's Orthodox Theological Seminary - Orthodox Musical Tradition, 2000-2005 (Box 52, Folder 320)
  - Salvation Army of Greater New York - Urban Youth Leadership Program, 2000-2004 (Box 52, Folder 321)
  - Salzburg Seminar - Asian Initiative, 2001-2005 (Box 52, Folder 322)
  - Salzburg Seminar - Asian Program Planning Grant, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 323)
  - Salzburg Seminar - Higher Education in Emerging Economies, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 324)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art - "The Art of Richard Tuttle" Exhibition, 2003-2007 (Box 54, Folder 332-334)
  - Scholars Press - Center for the Study and Advancement of Religion, 1996-2001 (Box 53, Folder 325-326)
  - School of Oriental and African Studies, University of London - Tibet Archives in Lhasa, 2003-2013 (Box 53, Folder 327)
  - School of Oriental and African Studies, University of London - Tibet Autonomous Regional Archives, 1998-2013 (Box 53, Folder 328-331)
  - School of Oriental and African Studies, University of London - Tibet Autonomous Regional Archives - International Tibetan Archives Preservation Project (ITAPP) (Box 53, Folder 328-331)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use and access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivists for further instruction.
  - Oscar Seagle Association - Music Colony Scholarships, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 335)
  - Seamen's Church Institute - International Training Center for Emerging Nation Maritime Ministries, 1997-1999 (Box 54, Folder 336-337)
  - Seamen's Church Institute - World Haven Initiative of the International Training Center, 1999-2003 (Box 54, Folder 338)
  - Seattle Art Museum - "Treasures of a Lost Civilization: Ancient Chinese Art from Sichuan" Exhibition and Catalog, 2000-2002 (Box 55, Folder 339)
  - Second Presbyterian Church - Alexander Robertson School, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 340)
  - Second Presbyterian Church - Restoration of the Austin Pipe Organ, 1999-2000 (Box 55, Folder 341)
  - Seminary Consortium for Urban Pastoral Education - "Nurturing the Call" Education Program for Urban Pastors, 2000-2003 (Box 55, Folder 342)
  - Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery and Sculpture Garden - Visiting Scholars Program (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1998-2005 (Box 55, Folder 343-344)
  - Sheltering Arms Children's Service - Upward After School Program, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 345)
  - Simmons College - Masters Program for Vietnam Librarians, 2000-2005 (Box 55, Folder 346)
  - Skidmore College - Distinguished Visiting Fellows (DVF) Program, 1996-2001 (Box 56, Folder 347)
  - Skidmore College - Object Exhibition and Knowledge Project, 2001-2007 (Box 56, Folder 348)
  - Smithsonian American Art Museum - "The Civil War and American Art" Exhibition and Catalog, 2011-2013 (Box 56, Folder 349-350)
  - Smithsonian Institution - Mekong River: Connecting Cultures Project, 2006-2013 (Box 56, Folder 351-352)
  - Smithsonian Institution - "Speak to my Heart: African American Communities of Faith and Contemporary Society", 1998-2004 (Box 57, Folder 353-354)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Center for Folklife Programs and Cultural Studies - Training Activities to Enhance Vietnamese Cultural Institutions, 1998-2005 (Box 57, Folder 355)
  - Society of Women Engineers - Create and Disseminate an Electronic Compendium of SWE's Collection of Literature Reviews, 2009-2013 (Box 57, Folder 356)
  - South Florida Center for Theological Studies - Theology through the Arts Program, 1998-2001 (Box 57, Folder 357-358)
  - J.B. Speed Art Museum - "Art and Soul: Spirituality in the 90s" Interfaith Education Through the Arts Program, 1996-2000 (Box 57, Folder 359)
  - Sponsors for Educational Opportunity - Career Program, 2000-2002 (Box 58, Folder 360)
  - Stanford University - Environmental Studies Graduate Program, 2001-2007 (Box 58, Folder 361)
  - Staten Island Botanical Garden - Chinese Scholar's Garden, 1997-2000 (Box 58, Folder 362-363)
  - Strawbery Banke - Collections Management Center, 2003-2006 (Box 58, Folder 364)
  - Stepping Stone Foundation - Scholars Program and Magnet Program, 1999-2003 (Box 58, Folder 365)
  - Student/Sponsor Partnership - High School Scholarships, 2000-2004 (Box 59, Folder 366-367)
  - Student/Sponsor Partnership - Parochial School Scholarships, 1997-2005 (Box 59, Folder 368)
  - Studio Museum, Harlem - African American Modernism, 1996-1999 (Box 59, Folder 369)
  - Studio Museum, Harlem - "Energy/Experimentation: Black Artists and Abstraction, 1964-1980" Exhibition and Catalog, 2005-2006 (Box 59, Folder 370)
  - Sustainability Institute - Sustainable Commodity Systems, 2000-2003 (Box 59, Folder 371-372)
  - Swarthmore College - "Christian Identity in Buddhist Thailand" Publication, 2000-2003 (Box 60, Folder 373-374)
  - Tacoma Art Museum - "The Great American Thing: Modern Art and National Identity, 1915-1935" Symposium, 2005-2006 (Box 60, Folder 375)
  - Teach for America - Expansion of the Teaching Corps, 2000-2003 (Box 60, Folder 376)
  - Temple of Understanding - Spiritual Journey: Interfaith Perspectives, 2000-2002 (Box 60, Folder 377)
  - Temple of Understanding - Educational Institution for Ministry in a Multifaith World, 2001-2004 (Box 60, Folder 378)
  - Temple University - Master of Laws Program for Chinese Students, 1999-2004 (Box 61, Folder 379-380)
  - Thai Support Foundation - Benefit Dinner, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 381)
  - Thirteen WNET - "New York: A Documentary Film" Produced by Steeplechase Films, 2000-2004 (Box 61, Folder 382)
  - Thomas Aquinas College - Interdisciplinary Faculty Position, 1994-2004 (Box 61, Folder 383)
  - Tibet Center - Educational Programs on Buddhism, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 384)
  - Tibet House U.S. - Educational Programs, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 385)
  - Toledo Museum of Art - Edwin D. Dodd, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 386)
  - Tricycle: The Buddhist Review - Director Mail Campaign, 1996-1997 (Box 61, Folder 387)
  - Tricycle: The Buddhist Review - "Change Your Mind Day", 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 388)
  - Tricycle: The Buddhist Review - Office Move, 1995-1997 (Box 61, Folder 389)
  - Tricycle: The Buddhist Review - Editorial Expansion and Redesign, 1999-2003 (Box 62, Folder 390)
  - Tufts University - Graduate Education for International Environmental Solutions Governance, 2002-2007 (Box 62, Folder 391)
  - Union Settlement Association - College Bound Center, 2000-2004 (Box 62, Folder 392)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Fellowships for Chinese Religious Studies Faculty, 1998-2005 (Box 62, Folder 393)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Theological Education in Asia, 2002-2004 (Box 62, Folder 394)
  - United Church of Christ - Vocational Identity and Leadership Program, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 395)
  - United Nations - "For a Better World" Poster Exhibition, 2001-2003 (Box 63, Folder 396)
  - United States-Indochina Reconciliation Project and Institute of International Exchange - Forum on Cambodia, Laos, and Vietnam, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 397)
  - United Theological Seminary of the Twin Cities - Developing Leadership in Religion and the Arts Program, 2000-2009 (Box 63, Folder 398-399)
  - United Theological Seminary of the Twin Cities - Religion and Arts Program, 1996-1998 (Box 63, Folder 400-401)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Book on Mongolian Transition, 1999-2004 (Box 63, Folder 402)
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Korean Christianity Program, 2000-2004 (Box 64, Folder 403-404)
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Southeast Asian Studies Librarian, 1999-2005 (Box 64, Folder 405)
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Southeast Asian Studies Program, 1996-2003 (Box 64, Folder 406)
  - University of California, Riverside - Southeast Asian Studies Program, 2001-2006 (Box 64, Folder 407)
  - University of Hartford, Hartford Seminary - Luce Forum in Abrahamic Religion, 1995-2003 (Box 64, Folder 408-410)
  - University of Maine - Lobster Shell Disease Study, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 411)
  - University of Maryland, College Park - Chinese Caligraphy and Painting Connoisseurship, 2000-2003 (Box 65, Folder 412-413)
  - University of Maryland, College Park - Chinese Language Field Initiative, 2001-2005 (Box 65, Folder 414)
  - University of Massachusetts, Dartmouth - Shanghai Chinese Business Archives, 2001-2002 (Box 65, Folder 415)
  - University of Massachusetts, Dartmouth - Microfilm and Catalog Shanghai Chinese Business Archives, 1999-2002 (Box 65, Folder 416-417)
  - University of Michigan - Asian Art Photographic Distribution Program, 1997-2003 (Box 65, Folder 418)
  - University of Michigan - "Traditional Japanese Music and Its Instruments" Music CD, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 419)
  - University of Montana - "Americas' Wars in Asia: A Cultural Approach" Program, 2000-2004 (Box 66, Folder 420-421)
  - University of Pennsylvania Museum of Archaeology and Anthropology - Thai Archaeology Publication Project, 1999-2004 (Box 66, Folder 422)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Chinese History and Culture CD-ROM, 1998-2001 (Box 66, Folder 423)
  - University of Puget Sound - Southeast Asian Studies Faculty Position, 1997-2002 (Box 66, Folder 424)
  - University of San Francisco, Ricci Institute - Christianity in China Database, 1996-2006 (Box 67, Folder 425-427)
  - University of Washington - Early Buddhist Manuscripts, 1999-2003 (Box 67, Folder 428-429)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum - Collection of American Paintings prior to 1945, 1983-1994 (Box 67, Folder 430)
  - Walker Art Center - Permanent Collection of American Paintings, Sculpture, and Drawings, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 431)
  - Wesley Theological Seminary - Douglass Lewis Center, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 432)
  - Wesley Theological Seminary - Center for the Arts and Religion, 2000-2006 (Box 68, Folder 433-434)
    - Exhibit VII: Culture at the Crossroads with Kojo Nnambi on NPR (Box T1)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Henry Francis du Pont Winterthur Museum - American Silver, 1985-1995 (Box 68, Folder 435)
  - Henry Francis du Pont Winterthur Museum - "New England Furniture at Winterthur: Queen Anne and Chippendale Periods" Publication, 1986-1997 (Box 68, Folder 436-437)
  - Women in Engineering Programs and Advocates Network (WEPAN) - National Conference, 2002-2003 (Box 68, Folder 438)
  - Yale University Art Gallery - Curatorial Sabbatical, 2003-2004 (Box 68, Folder 439)